<resources>
    <!-- Name of app -->
    <string name="app_name">Healthy Helper</string>

    <!-- Splash screen app name -->
    <string name="healthyHelperSplashScreen">Healthy Helper</string>

    <!-- Main menu components -->
    <string name="mainMenuTitleText">Press a Button Below to Access a Feature</string>
    <string name="mainMenuArticlesButton">Articles</string>
    <string name="mainMenuBloodGlucoseRecorderButton">Blood Glucose Recorder</string>
    <string name="mainMenuRecipesButton">Recipes</string>
    <string name="mainMenuShoppingCartButton">Shopping\nCart</string>
    <string name="mainMenuHowToUseAppButton">How to use app</string>

    <!-- Articles menu components -->
    <string name="articlesMenuWhatIsPreDiabetesTitle">What is Pre Diabetes?</string>
    <string name="articlesMenuEatingHealthyWithDiabetesTitle">Eating Healthy With Diabetes</string>
    <string name="articlesMenuKeepingActiveWithDiabetesTitle">Keeping Active With Diabetes</string>

    <!-- Articles components -->
    <string name="articleWhatIsPrediabetesHyperlink">For more information please <a href="https://www2.hse.ie/conditions/pre-diabetes/">visit the HSE website here</a></string>
    <string name="articleWhatIsPreDiabetes">Pre-diabetes is a condition where the amount of glucose (sugar) in the blood is higher than normal but is not high enough for you to have a diagnosis of type 2 diabetes. Pre-diabetes while treatable should be taken very seriously as careful management of the condition can prevent or delay a type 2 diagnosis. The earlier pre-diabetes is diagnosed the better.\n\n Many people have pre-diabetes without realising it due to a lack of symptoms. High blood glucose levels can develop gradually over time without ever being noticed. If you have any of the signs or symptoms of high blood glucose, it is possible you may already have Type 2 diabetes. See a GP if you have any symptoms of diabetes or you\'re worried you may have a risk of getting it as this can be checked via a blood test.\n\n The risks for developing pre-diabetes are the same risks as those for Type 2 diabetes, that being if you \n • Are over 45. \n • Have a close relative with diabetes such as a parent, brother or sister. \n • Are an adult who has overweight or obesity - check your body mass index (BMI). \n • Had gestational diabetes during pregnancy. \n • Are physically inactive - for example, if you take less than 30 minutes of physical activity 5 days per week. \n • Have high blood pressure, high cholesterol, low HDL cholesterol or high triglycerides. \n • Have a history of heart disease. \n • Have a medical condition that requires long-term steroid use. \n • Are a member of the travelling community. \n • Are of south Asian, Chinese, Hispanic, African Caribbean or black African origin. \n • Have haemochromatosis - storing too much iron in your body. \n • Are a woman with polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS).\n\n If you have a diagnosis of pre-diabetes, by acting now you can delay or potentially prevent developing type 2 diabetes. This can be done by \n • Being more active and reduce long periods of time sitting. \n • Losing weight. \n • Eating healthy food. \n • Having regular check-ups as advised by your GP or practice nurse.\n\n Calculate your body mass index (BMI) online or via your GP is important to check your current health. Also checking your waist size is useful to see if you are carrying any excess weight. This can put extra pressure on the pancreas and liver which can greatly increase your risk of developing diabetes.</string>
    <string name="articleEatingHealthyWithDiabetesHyperlink">For more information please <a href="https://www2.hse.ie/conditions/type-2-diabetes/living-with/eating-healthy/">visit the HSE website here</a></string>
    <string name="articleEatingHealthyWithDiabetesMainText">Eating the right and right amounts of food is a critical part in both the prevention of type 2 as well as managing of a type 2 diagnosis. One can take several measures in order to help manage their diets as best as possible.\n\n Eating 3 regular meals a day every day is vital as skipping meals may increase your snack intake or increase portions of later meals.\n\n Limiting of processed foods such as foods that are high in fat, salt etc as they generally have little to no nutritional value, increasing the likelihood of extra snacking. Eating fresh food, frozen food along with generally healthier options are far more beneficial to you while helping to make you feel less hungry.\n\nSome of these options include. \n • Fruit and vegetables. \n • Milk, yogurt, and cheese. \n • Fish such as salmon, sardines, trout etc. \n • Lean meat such as chicken and turkey. \n • Eggs. \n • Small portions of nuts and seeds. \n • Healthy fats and oils such as reduced fat or light spreads, rapeseed oil, olive oil etc.\n\n Choosing wholegrain varieties of foods such as bread, cereal etc due to being less refined helping to provide the body with a source of fibre.\n\n Importantly foods that are labelled as diabetic friendly or suitable for diabetics are not a guarantee of as these foods may still be high in fat, processed sugars etc.\n\n Choosing sugar free foods helps to reduce the total of carbohydrates into the body. Carbohydrates directly affect your blood glucose levels as the body breaks them down and turns them into glucose in the bloodstream, so it is vital to closely analyse how much carbohydrates you consume.\n\nCarbohydrate foods. \n • Cereal and porridge. \n • All breads such as white, brown, rolls etc. \n • Scones and crackers. \n • Potatoes and related products such as chips, crisps etc. \n • Rice, pasta, and noodles. \n • Foods containing flour. \n • Fruit. Fruit juice, milk, and yogurt (these contain natural carbohydrates and sugars). \n • Desserts such as ice cream, buns etc. \n • Cakes, sweets, and biscuits. \n • Alcohol.\n\n Changing your whole diet can be hard so it is important to get help where it is needed whether this be from medical practitioners or from friends and family. Contact your GP to reference to a dietitian for advice on where to start or for additional support if required.\n\n Organisations such as the HSE also run support free courses for type 2 diabetes which can also be applied to a pre-diabetes diagnosis. It can be difficult to make such drastic changes but by starting now, you can improve both your health and quality of life.</string>
    <string name="articleKeepingActiveWithDiabetesHyperlink">For more information please <a href="https://www2.hse.ie/conditions/type-2-diabetes/living-with/keeping-active/">visit the HSE website here</a></string>
    <string name="articleKeepingActiveWithDiabetesMainText">Being active is very beneficial when it comes to preventing and living with type 2 diabetes, helping to lower your blood glucose, pressure, and cholesterol. Remaining active also helps to reduce body fat.\n\n A simple, consistent routine of exercise is vital for remaining active for example for example 30 minutes of moderate aerobic activity (enough to get the heart and lungs working faster but still feel relatively comfortable for example being able to hold a conversation) at least 5 days a week. Generally, the more exercise you do the better however it may be worthwhile to contact your GP for advice if it is too uncomfortable.\n\n Examples of moderate aerobic activity include. \n • Walking at a brisk pace \n • Cycling \n • Swimming \n • Garden work such as digging \n • Dancing\n\n Breaking up long periods of sitting is also vital in keeping active such as when in front of the computer. Standing up every half an hour or even better going short 2-to-3-minute walk can help assist in lowering blood glucose levels.</string>
    <string name="articlesResetZoomButton">Reset Zoom</string>

    <!-- Blood glucose recorder components -->
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderTimeTextbox">Time</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderGlucoseLevelTextbox">Glucose Level</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderEnterReadingButton">Enter Reading</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderRemoveReadingButton">Remove Reading</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderViewReadingButton">View Readings</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderDateTextbox">Date</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderLoadDateButton">Load Date</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderAddDateButton">Add Date</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderViewDatesButton">View Dates</string>
    <string name="bloodGlucoseRecorderRemoveDateButton">Remove Date</string>

    <!-- Recipes menu components -->
    <string name="recipesMenuBreakfastFilterButton">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuLunchFilterButton">Lunch</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuDinnerFilterButton">Dinner</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuDessertFilterButton">Dessert</string>
    <string name="recipesCrunchyBlueberryYogurtDescription">Crunchy Blueberry Yogurt: \nCooking time 2 mins \nTags: Gluten free, Dairy</string>
    <string name="recipesHummusDescription">Hummus: \nCooking time 5 mins \nTags: Gluten free, Vegan, Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="recipesSalmonRiceBowlDescription">Salmon Rice Bowl : \nCooking time 15 mins \nTags: Gluten free</string>
    <string name="recipesPoachedPearsDescription">Poached Pears: \nCooking time 15–20 mins \nTags: Gluten free, Vegan, Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuFilterBreakfast">BREAKFAST</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuFilterLunch">LUNCH</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuFilterDinner">DINNER</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuFilterDessert">DESSERT</string>
    <string name="recipesMenuResetFiltersButton">Reset Filters</string>

    <!-- Recipes components -->
    <string name="recipeCrunchyBlueBerryYogurtRecipeHyperlink">This recipe <a href="https://www.diabetes.ie/living-with-diabetes/living-with-type-2/food-diabetes/recipes/breakfast/crunchy-blueberry-yoghurt/">from Diabetes Ireland is available here</a></string>
    <string name="recipeCrunchyBlueberryYogurtMainText">Cooking time: 2 mins\nTags: Gluten free, Dairy\n \nNutritional analysis per serving: \nCalories (kcal) 218 \nProtein (g) 10.2 \nTotal Carbohydrates (g) 36.1 \nOf Which Sugars (g) 14.9 \nFat (g) 3.7 \nSaturated fat (g) 0.9 \nFibre (g) 3.8 \nSodium (g) 0.1 \nSalt equivalent (g) 0.3 \n\nINGREDIENTS \n • 1 small pot of natural yogurt (125g) \n • 3 tablespoons of fresh blueberries \n • 2 tablespoons of muesli \n\nMETHOD\n \nSTEP 1: Mix everything together and eat immediately.\n \nNOTE: any combination of fruit could be used for this recipe. However, make sure you count the total amount of carbohydrates being put into the recipe.</string>
    <string name="recipeHummusRecipeHyperlink">This recipe <a href="https://www.bbcgoodfood.com/recipes/hummus">from BBC good food is available here</a></string>
    <string name="recipeHummusMainText">Cooking time: 10 mins\nTags: Gluten-free, Vegan, Vegetarian\n \nNutritional analysis per serving: \nEnergy (kcal) 380 \nProtein (g) 7 \nTotal Carbohydrates (g) 9 \nOf Which Sugars (g) 0.4 \nFat (g) 28 \nSaturated fat (g) 4 \nFibre (g) 5 \nSalt equivalent (g) 0.01 \n\nINGREDIENTS \n • 1 can chickpeas drained. \n • 60ml cold water plus a 30ml for a looser consistency. \n • 1 small garlic clove peeled and crushed. \n • 1 lemon juiced then 1/2 zested. \n • 3 tbsp tahini. \n • 1 tbsp olive oil to garnish (optional). \n • Mixed crudites and toasted pitta bread to serve (optional). \n\nMETHOD\n \nSTEP 1: Thoroughly rinse the chickpeas in a colander under cold running water. Tip into the large bowl of a food processor along with 60ml of water and blitz until almost smooth. Add the garlic, lemon and tahini and blitz again. if the consistency is too thick, Gradually pour in up to 30ml more water then blitz again for about 5 mins or until the hummus is smooth and silky.\n \nSTEP 2: Season with a good pinch of sea salt and transfer to a bowl. Swirl the top of the hummus with the back of a dessert spoon and drizzle over a little olive oil. Serve with crunchy crudités and toasted pitta bread if you like.</string>
    <string name="recipeSalmonRiceBowlRecipeHyperlink">This recipe <a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7960938/salmon-rice-bowl/">from Eating Well is available here</a></string>
    <string name="recipeSalmonRiceBowlMainText">Cooking time: 15–20 mins\nTags: Gluten free\n \nNutritional analysis per serving: \nCalories 481 \nProtein (g) 18 \nTotal Carbohydrates (g) 47 \nOf Which Sugars (g) 3 \nFat (g) 25 \nSaturated fat (g) 4 \nFibre (g) 6 \nSodium (mg) 687 \n\nINGREDIENTS \n • 4 ounces salmon, preferably wild \n • 1 teaspoon avocado oil \n • 1/8 teaspoon kosher salt \n • 1 cup instant brown rice \n • 1 cup water \n • 2 tablespoons mayonnaise \n • 1 1/2 teaspoons Sriracha \n • 1 1/2 teaspoons 50%-less-sodium tamari \n • 1 teaspoon mirin \n • 1/2 teaspoon freshly grated ginger \n • 1/4 teaspoon crushed red pepper \n • 1/2 ripe avocado, chopped \n • 1/2 cup chopped cucumber \n • 1/4 cup spicy kimchi \n • 12 (4-inch) sheets nori (roasted seaweed) \n\nMETHOD\n \nSTEP 1: Preheat oven to 400ºF. Line a small, rimmed baking sheet with foil. Place salmon on the prepared pan. Drizzle with oil; season with salt. Bake until an instant-read thermometer inserted in the thickest part registers 125ºF, 8 to 10 minutes.\n \nSTEP 2: Meanwhile, combine rice and water in a small saucepan; cook according to package directions. Mix mayonnaise and Sriracha in a small bowl; set aside. Whisk tamari, mirin, ginger, crushed red pepper and salt in another small bowl; set aside.\n \nSTEP 3: Divide the rice between 2 bowls. Top with salmon, avocado, cucumber, and kimchi. Drizzle with the tamari mixture and the mayonnaise mixture. Mix the bowls, if desired, and serve with nori.</string>
    <string name="recipePoachedPearsRecipeHyperlink">This recipe <a href="https://www.diabetes.ie/living-with-diabetes/living-with-type-2/food-diabetes/recipes/desserts/poached-pears/">from Diabetes Ireland is available here</a></string>
    <string name="recipePoachedPearsMainText">Cooking time: 15–20 mins\nTags: Gluten free, Vegetarian\n \nNutritional analysis per serving: \nEnergy (kcal) 216 \nProtein (g) 7.3 \nTotal Carbohydrates (g) 27.5 \nOf Which Sugars (g) 26.8 \nFat (g) 9.3 \nSaturated fat (g) 1.2 \nFibre (g) 4.6 \nSodium (mg) 55 \nSalt equivalent (g) 0.1 \n\nINGREDIENTS \n • 200ml apple juice. \n • 1 cinnamon stick. \n • 4 just–ripe pears halved length ways, and cores removed. \n • 60g flaked almonds, toasted. \n • 300g low fat natural yogurt. \n\nMETHOD \n\nSTEP 1: Put the apple juice and cinnamon stick into a saucepan, along with 200ml water and 200ml apple juice. Bring to the boil. \n\nSTEP 2: Reduce to a simmer and add the pears. Cover with a lid and cook for 10–15 mins, or until the pears are tender. Remove the pears using a slotted spoon and set aside. \n\nSTEP 3: Bring the remaining juice to the boil and reduce volume by half. \n\nSTEP 4: To serve, place half a pear in the centre of a plate, top with yoghurt and flaked almonds, and spoon a little of the reduced juice around the edge.</string>
    <string name="recipesResetZoomButton">Reset Zoom</string>
    <string name="recipesAddRecipeToShoppingCartButton">Add recipe to shopping cart</string>

    <!-- Shopping cart menu components -->
    <string name="shoppingCartMenuTitleText">Currently Tracked Recipes</string>

    <!-- Shopping cart components -->
    <string name="shoppingCartCrunchyBlueberryYogurtTags">Gluten free, Dairy</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartBlueberryYogurtIngredient1">1 Small pot of natural yogurt (125g)</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartBlueberryYogurtIngredient2">3 tablespoons of fresh blueberries</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartBlueberryYogurtIngredient3">2 tablespoons of muesli</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartBlueberryYogurtDescription">You can add more or less of the above mentioned ingredients to this recipe or even add your own. \n\nHowever make sure to keep an eye on the amount of carbohydrates being added</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusTags">Gluten Free, Dairy Free, Vegan, Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient1">1 can of drained chickpeas</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient2">60ml Cold Water (additional 30ml for looser consistency)</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient3">1 small garlic clove</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient4">1 lemon</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient5">3 tablespoons of tahini</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient6">(Optional) 1 tablespoon of olive oil</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient7">(Optional) mixed crudités</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartHummusIngredient8">(Optional) Toasted pitta bread</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlTags">Gluten free</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient1">4 ounces salmon, preferably wild</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient2">1 teaspoon avocado oil</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient3">1/8 teaspoon kosher salt</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient4">1 cup instant brown rice</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient5">1 cup water</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient6">2 tablespoons mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient7">1 1/2 teaspoons Sriracha</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient8">1 1/2 teaspoons 50%-less-sodium tamari</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient9">1 teaspoon mirin</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient10">1/2 teaspoon freshly grated ginger</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient11">1/4 teaspoon crushed red pepper</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient12">1/2 ripe avocado, chopped</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient13">1/2 cup chopped cucumber</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient14">1/4 cup spicy kimchi</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartSalmonRiceBowlIngredient15">12 (4-inch) sheets nori (roasted seaweed)</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartPoachedPearsTags">Gluten free, Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartPoachedPearsIngredient1">200ml Apple Juice</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartPoachedPearsIngredient2">1 cinnamon stick</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartPoachedPearsIngredient3">4 just-ripe pears halved length ways and cores cut</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartPoachedPearsIngredient4">60g flaked almonds toasted</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartPoachedPearsIngredient5">300g low fat natural yogurt</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartInstructions">To mark off an ingredient, press an ingredient\nTo undo hold the ingredient</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartResetShoppingCartButton">Reset Shopping Cart</string>

    <!-- How to use components -->
    <string name="howToUseArticlesButton">Articles</string>
    <string name="howToUseBloodGlucoseRecorderButton">Recorder</string>
    <string name="howToUseRecipesButton">Recipes</string>
    <string name="howToUseShoppingCartButton">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="howToUseIntroText">Please press one of the buttons above to access the relevant instructions.</string>
    <string name="howToUseArticlesText">Once you have found an article you are interested in reading and pressed its appropriate icon, the article will open on screen. Pressing the link on top of the screen will bring you to the source of the article via your mobile phones web browser (this requires some form of internet connection such as data or WI-FI).\n\n You can view the whole contents of the article by swiping the screen with one finger up/down to scroll the text down/up. The size of the text can also be increased or decreased by pinching the screen with two fingers. NOTE: USING MORE THAN ONE OR TWO FINGERS CAN LEAD TO INCORRECT FUNCTIONALITY.\n\n Finally, if you wish to reset the text’s size to its original, you can either leave the article and come back to it or you can press the “Reset Zoom” button on the bottom of the screen, this will require two presses to function to prevent accidentally losing your progress.</string>
    <string name="howToUseBloodGlucoseRecorderText">Upon opening this feature, you will be greeted to a graph with a visible X axis representing the 24 hour clock (The Y axis shall appear upon adding an entry to the graph). At the bottom of the screen, you can see there are four buttons along with a text box called “Date”.\n\n By pressing said text box a calendar dialog box will appear which is then used to pick the date you wish to record a reading for. You are unable to enter a date that is beyond what is on your phone for example if today is the 2nd of April you cannot plot for the 3rd of April etc until the new day begins which will be shown via a message.\n\n The currently saved dates can be viewed by pressing the “View Dates” button which presents a dialog box containing each entry. This will show the saved dates or if there are currently no saved dates.\n\n To load a date, you need to select a valid date from the dialog box then press “Load Date”. However, if this date has not been previously added before, you are required to press the “Add Date” button just to the right. To remove a previously saved date, this can be done by pressing the “Remove Date” button, NOTE: FOR DATA SAFETY REMOVING A DATE WILL NOT DELETE THE ENTRIES THE ENTERED IN THE TABLE, EACH READING WILL NEED TO BE REMOVED INDIVIDUALLY WHICH WILL BE COVERED WITHIN THE NEXT TWO PARAGRAPHS.\n\n Upon loading a date, 3 new buttons along with 2 new text boxes will appear on the screen. This is where the actual time and glucose reading are recorded. To plot an entry first press the “Time” text box and pick a time from the on-screen time clock dialog box, then plot the reading recorded from your glucose meter and finally press the “Enter Reading” button. If this reading is at a normal level it will appear as a green bar on the bar chart, if it is close to excessive reading this will appear as a orange bar while a dangerous reading will appear as a red bar on the bar chart.\n\n You are unable to plot more than one entry at a specific time on the bar chart so to remove an entry, select the time you wish to remove then press the “Remove Reading” button. If the bars end up becoming too bunched up or difficult to read by pressing the “View Readings” button you will be able to see every entry that has been added along with an identifier (OK, WARNING, DANGER) next to a normal reading, close to excessive or a dangerous reading respectfully.\n\n Similarly, to the shopping cart every date, entry etc will be saved in memory unless the application has been uninstalled or had its storage deleted.\n\n While this may appear daunting there will be messages that will appear at the bottom of the screen which will help to guide you every step of the way, you will be a natural in no time.</string>
    <string name="howToUseRecipesText">Each of the available recipes can be filtered by one of the 4 filter buttons located on top of the screen. Upon selecting one of the filters (Breakfast, Dinner etc) meals matching that filter will remain while those which don’t will be slightly faded with the required filter appearing as text. Attempting to press one of these faded recipes will present you with a message of which filter to press. The filters can be reset by leaving the recipes page and going back into it or by pressing the “Reset Filters” button on the bottom of the screen.\n\n In a similar fashion to the articles section, once you have found a recipe you are interested in reading and pressed its appropriate icon the recipe will open on screen. Pressing the green link on top of the screen will bring you to the source of the article via your mobile phones web browser (this requires some form of internet connection such as data or WI-FI).\n\n You can view the whole contents of the recipe by swiping the screen with one finger up/down to scroll the text down/up. The size of the text can also be increased or decreased by pinching the screen with two fingers. NOTE: USING MORE THAN ONE OR TWO FINGERS CAN LEAD TO INCORRECT FUNCTIONALITY.\n\n if you wish to reset the text’s size to its original, you can either leave the article and come back to it or you can press the “Reset Zoom” button on the bottom of the screen, this will require two presses to function to prevent accidentally losing your progress.\n\n Finally if you are interested in attempting to cook the recipe, you can press the “Add This Recipes Ingredients to the Shopping Cart” button, this will break down the recipes ingredients and place them into the shopping cart indicated by a message on the bottom of the screen. To remove a recipe long press the same button, a message will appear indicating the recipe has been removed.</string>
    <string name="howToUseShoppingCartText">As previously mentioned in the recipes section, once you have found a recipe you are interested in reading and have pressed its appropriate icon the recipe will open on screen. You can press the “Add This Recipes Ingredients to the Shopping Cart” button located on the bottom of the screen which breaks down the recipes ingredients and places them into the shopping cart indicated by a message on the bottom of the screen (or removed via a long press). This will add an entry into the shopping cart where the ingredients can be accessed.\n\n From here a user can remove an ingredient they have purchased or have around the house for whatever reason by pressing one of the yellow buttons containing an ingredient. If this was accidental or it turns out you don’t have enough, long pressing a removed ingredient will re-add the ingredient. If you wish to re-add all the ingredients this can be done by pressing the “Reset Shopping Cart” button on the bottom of the screen.\n\n You do not need to worry about keeping record of which ingredients you have or have not removed as the application will save which have been or have not been removed unless the application has been uninstalled or had its storage deleted.</string>
    <string name="howToUseResetZoomButton">Reset Zoom</string>

    <!-- Overflow menu items -->
    <string name="articlesOverflowMenu">Articles</string>
    <string name="blood_recorderOverflowMenu">Blood Recorder</string>
    <string name="recipesOverflowMenu">Recipes</string>
    <string name="shoppingCartOverflowMenu">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="mainMenuOverflowMenu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="howToUseAppOverflowMenu">How to Use App</string>
</resources>
